hello everybody and welcome to this
video today I want to present you the Z
MIDI basically it's a stereoscopic
camera that allow you if you merge it
with the oculus at the back back to do
crazy project so this video is just
telling about the research and the
result I've done basically stills could
be run during and as you can see if you
cross your eyes
it's crazy it's precise you can really
feel the object touch it have a feeling
of reality
now you can feed your hand you can do
crazy stuff like serving you a tea you
know - hot stuff and the precision is so
good that I'm trusting - it's based on
the telescopic image and give you a 3d
model in real time that is not based on
infrared so you can scan outside you can
just can't really model that is metal
one so it's perfect to scan any objects
so I was wondering can I scan a shoes or
small objects and yes it does but mainly
it will scan a room so my second
question was okay can i scan the room
and in a how many time and as you can
see it's kind of perfect for kangaroo
because it take less than a minute and
you have the shape the volume and the 3d
mesh at the end you can record it with
the texture if you want you can record
it raw if you want and you can choose
the precision if you want something
better or 20 centimeter so for example
for this chair it was a bit better than
the small objects you have the shape you
have the texture
all you need to be able to do a tweety
bowl a little bit so i detroy know so
small object check if it is me who is
carrying badly but as you can see yeah
it's perfect to scan just the idea of
the objects but I don't think I will be
able to scan a small object with this
kind of device maybe we'll try my other
try was to scan myself because I really
want to be able to scan the size of the
guy in a quick manner Oh at least to be
able to scan the body and animate it but
it was a fail again but I think it's
just a matter of time for this one
because it's perfect so I was like okay
I will try to scan outside to see the
distant I can scan and as you can see I
have bike and if you wonder am I crazy
no I'm not because indeed it's still
here scope in camera and so what you
don't understand is that when you are on
the bike with this kind of camera you
really are on a bike like in reality so
I feel the deep I feel the distance and
it's impossible for me to fall off the
bike as you can see it's kind of crazy
the perfection you can have because here
I did ask the scanning to be 20
centimeter and as you can see I can scan
a street in less than 2 minutes just
walking in the street and bam I has a 3d
model of it so during my test that it
try lots of objects like your by bike
like the wall and stuff like this
and it works each time good but not good
enough to do a 3d model of it so you
really need to edit it the good part is
that you can scan just watch some object
and recalled the environment and then
asked to do the 3d rendering when you
are back home for example here I did
recall just the church and a guy and at
the home I was doing the 3d model as you
can see it's were kind of better than my
first test with the guy but he was
moving and so the 3d model is kind of
true but yeah it work well so people
have interests they ask a lot of
question about it and they are not
afraid of you running in the street with
a bike and a lot of equipment on your
face I suppose that they are used to
Google's
so here is the model in unity of the 3d
scanner as you can see it's kind of good
for the time I scan because ten seconds
scanning here and as you can see for the
road the scan is kind of super cool
because the 3d model is not totally
completed but at least the proportion
and the measurement are perfect because
if there is mixed reality positional
tracking that is working really really
well also I meet me I meet some people
on the road and as you can see they were
a bit surprised ninety and so yeah I
will try a lot of experiment like doing
the dishes and playing BR and doing
crazy stuff so don't hesitate to ask
questions participate to propose me some
experiments you would like me to try
with the equipment and ask any question
in the commentary I will be glad and so
yeah have a nice day
feel free to contact me and I will see
you later bye if you want to be aware of
what I'm doing and the news don't
hesitate to become a patreon and stay
crazy please stay crazy
you